Okay.
When you listen to that reporting of Tory Lanez apologizing to Kelsey,
there are some basic things that are going to be said.
Something I hear a lot of people saying is,
you know, when I hear that recording,
it sounds like he's apologizing for something else.
When he is saying,
I think it was just too much when I got to, when I got to that house.
That lets you know that the context of his conversation is about what's happening that night.
Now, when people are like, oh, well, he could be apologizing for anything that happened that night.
Okay. He then also says,
I know she probably never, ever gonna talk to me ever again, but.
This is what I'm talking about with contact.
Him stating that is a thing that happened that night.
Well, you know, Kelsey is because why would you answer the phone of somebody who just shot your friend?
Now, as somebody who has had a rapper extort them for money by using a picture
that was not taken with my consent.
And then when they called me, I still answered the phone.
I can understand because.
Yep. If you want to hear what else I got to say, you got to go to my Patreon, theamandaverse.com.
I can't give it all the way here, but I did do 10 minutes worth of it.
So it is very thorough.
So I'll see you there with me and the seal squad, but you did it, but I'm bad.